{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":11,"End":16,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Xfm 104.9. Steve just back announce that for us."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Good."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Okay."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":12,"End":16,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"We’ve got Song for the Lovers err, any minute now."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":31,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"We’ve got Song for the Lovers err, any minute now."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Uh and-"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":3,"End":9,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"PJ Harvey - This is Love"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":47,"End":65,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"PJ Harvey. This is Love. Xfm 104.9. It’s the Ricky Gervais Show innit?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":5,"End":19,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"With Steve Merchant."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":40,"End":45,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Yep. But you’re gonna keep quiet now, Steve. Because I’ve gotta do my- my world famous film review."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Mmm mmm."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Good."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve make jingle sound effects"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":10,"End":15,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve make jingle sound effects"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Haha. OK. Do you write these yourself?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Nope."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Okay okay. And what would you give that one out of five?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":29,"End":35,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"That’s a nine out of five. Strong review there. Strong film then for you."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":29,"End":35,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"That’s a nine out of five. Strong review there. Strong film then for you."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":10,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Jungle Book."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":10,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Jungle Book. Jolly good. Alright. Thanks very much for that."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":32,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Jungle Book. Jolly good. Alright. Thanks very much for that."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":29,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Well now it’s time for Song for the Lovers, this is The Smiths and Last Night I Dreamt Somebody Loved Me."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":44,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Well now it’s time for Song for the Lovers, this is The Smiths and Last Night I Dreamt Somebody Loved Me."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":58,"End":64,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Well now it’s time for Song for the Lovers, this is The Smiths and Last Night I Dreamt Somebody Loved Me."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Good, okay, cool, yeayeayea, lovely."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":10,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"The Smiths - Last Night I Dreamt That Somebody Loved Me begins to play"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":55,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"The Smiths - Last Night I Dreamt That Somebody Loved Me begins to play"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":10,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"The Smiths - Last Night I Dreamt That Somebody Loved Me"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":55,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"The Smiths - Last Night I Dreamt That Somebody Loved Me"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Smiths. Lovely song, Last Night I Dreamed Somebody Loved Me."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Beautiful."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Song for the Lovers there. On Xfm 104.9. Can’t believe I forgot the elephants. That is- that was key-"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":24,"End":35,"Label":"ORGANIZATION"}],"Text":"-element of the review, really.Yeah. Yeah."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":29,"End":33,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Don’t let it get you down, Rick. I know how these things depress you before-"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":58,"End":62,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"You stew about it. Um, played a beautiful song there. Uh, Song for the Lovers."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":71,"End":77,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"You stew about it. Um, played a beautiful song there. Uh, Song for the Lovers."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":206,"End":214,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And uh, you know I do get depressed when I see people around who’ve got girlfriends and I think- You know, cuz I haven’t and I don’t know what’s the rule. We mentioned last week that fat bloke from Pop Idol. He’s got a bird, which annoys me, angers me. And um, this really depressed me; walking into Piccadilly Circus tube a couple nights ago. Homeless guy, wrapped up, unwashed. And uh, Northern."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":310,"End":327,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And uh, you know I do get depressed when I see people around who’ve got girlfriends and I think- You know, cuz I haven’t and I don’t know what’s the rule. We mentioned last week that fat bloke from Pop Idol. He’s got a bird, which annoys me, angers me. And um, this really depressed me; walking into Piccadilly Circus tube a couple nights ago. Homeless guy, wrapped up, unwashed. And uh, Northern."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":398,"End":406,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And uh, you know I do get depressed when I see people around who’ve got girlfriends and I think- You know, cuz I haven’t and I don’t know what’s the rule. We mentioned last week that fat bloke from Pop Idol. He’s got a bird, which annoys me, angers me. And um, this really depressed me; walking into Piccadilly Circus tube a couple nights ago. Homeless guy, wrapped up, unwashed. And uh, Northern."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":162,"End":167,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And I sort- I lingered for a bit. I was thinking “What?!” And he was going “Yeah-“. Basically I pieced together that he’s got a girlfriend- He’s from Leeds- He’s got a girlfriend who’s also homeless, who’s homeless up in Leeds. And occasionally she kind of homelesses her way down to London."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":302,"End":308,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And I sort- I lingered for a bit. I was thinking “What?!” And he was going “Yeah-“. Basically I pieced together that he’s got a girlfriend- He’s from Leeds- He’s got a girlfriend who’s also homeless, who’s homeless up in Leeds. And occasionally she kind of homelesses her way down to London."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":8,"End":16,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I know! Pathetic. Oh, I angered that they’re could be-"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":35,"End":40,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Is there a lot of cheap housing in Leeds? Would that ruin it for him?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":57,"End":61,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"I mean it’s so- I’m mean that’s really depressing, Karl isn’t it? Unless they became smackheads together."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Karl. No. Karl’s found love on the street before, haven’t ya?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Karl. No. Karl’s found love on the street before, haven’t ya?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":32,"End":36,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"How’s it going with your bird Karl? Are you married? How long you’ve been out with her?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":33,"End":38,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And in a nice way. You’re like Helen from Big Brother. You’re sort of nice enough but-"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky sniggers."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Karl laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Alright. Jeez. I like the fact that he doesn’t want to talk about his love affair."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":170,"End":175,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I was- I was thinking about you in the week. And like… Does it worry you- I mean you sort of joke about it now when we talk about it in the office. You know like “Is Steve really touchy about the way he looks?”"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ooo hoo! You did start it though, didn’t ya?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":74,"End":77,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"No because I- for me, ya know- a lightweight frothy entertainment show on Xfm on a Saturday afternoon is exactly the place where I want to discuss the desperate lonely future that’s inevitably coming my way."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Oh god, I tell you what would cheer you up, to forget about it all. A bit of Embrace"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Embrace – Make it Last"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Hives, Main Offender, before that Embrace, Make it Last -- I know you don't like Embrace much, but that's a nice tune."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":7,"End":20,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Hives, Main Offender, before that Embrace, Make it Last -- I know you don't like Embrace much, but that's a nice tune."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":34,"End":41,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Hives, Main Offender, before that Embrace, Make it Last -- I know you don't like Embrace much, but that's a nice tune."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":34,"End":41,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Hives, Main Offender, before that Embrace, Make it Last -- I know you don't like Embrace much, but that's a nice tune."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":6,"End":10,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Yeah. Very nice. What, what - could you do better? I was mucking around..."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky plays with mic"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":53,"End":62,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I was thinking of just doing that, and sending it to John Peel. Maybe with some samples of like politicians going \"We will not t..aaar aar aaa\""}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ooh-hoo!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"X-Ray."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"X-Ray - what's X-Ray?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":9,"End":12,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"It's the Xfm magazine, Steve."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":23,"End":28,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"It's the Xfm magazine, Steve."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":8,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Magazine."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":22,"End":31,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"It's, it's in, er Top Magazines,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":29,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"You're really selling it Karl, you're obviously a fan of the magazine."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ok, cool!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Cool."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Centre pages."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Rick, I don't know if you're aware of this, but we have some tickets to give away. Is your favourite band, Marc E Smith's The Fall?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":107,"End":119,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Rick, I don't know if you're aware of this, but we have some tickets to give away. Is your favourite band, Marc E Smith's The Fall?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":50,"End":68,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"I thought it was, and is your favourite venue the Kentish Town Forum?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Ohh I'd see anything there –"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":125,"End":130,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I'd see The Fall anywhere, and I'd see anything there, so if you're telling me The Fall are there, we're not giving’m away Steve. I'd like those for m’self."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Rick, I'm just trying to remember if your favourite support act of late is \"Schindler\"?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Aww ...no I hate 'em."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":17,"End":26,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I'm only joking, Schindler, I'm only joking by the way. To Schindler, to the lads in Schindler, if they think I'm being a little bit nasty."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":17,"End":26,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"I'm only joking, Schindler, I'm only joking by the way. To Schindler, to the lads in Schindler, if they think I'm being a little bit nasty."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":46,"End":55,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Three pairs is it? Um, have you -- talking of Schindler, you know the, the people that make lifts, or, I think, escalators as well"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":46,"End":55,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Like in the bottom of a lift, it always says \"Schindler\". It's always made by some organisation called Schi-- do you think it's the same Schindler, like from Schindler's list?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":46,"End":55,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Like in the bottom of a lift, it always says \"Schindler\". It's always made by some organisation called Schi-- do you think it's the same Schindler, like from Schindler's list?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":8,"End":16,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"So it's Shindler's lifts."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":8,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Shindler's lifts."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":21,"End":30,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"“You're joking!” Spielberg was going \"I've made a whole film about them!”"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":47,"End":50,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"It was 3 hours, it was in black and white, for God's sake."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Anyway, next time you're in a lift, check that out, that is true. Anyway, we've got 3 tickets for The, uh, Fall, sorry, 3 pairs of tickets for The Fall who are performing tonight, at the Kentish Town Forum, if you'd like to win them, here's a question for you - which Radio 1, rival station, which Radio 1 personality used to be a member of The Fall. If you know then you can get in touch on 087008001234."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Anyway, next time you're in a lift, check that out, that is true. Anyway, we've got 3 tickets for The, uh, Fall, sorry, 3 pairs of tickets for The Fall who are performing tonight, at the Kentish Town Forum, if you'd like to win them, here's a question for you - which Radio 1, rival station, which Radio 1 personality used to be a member of The Fall. If you know then you can get in touch on 087008001234."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":107,"End":111,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Anyway, next time you're in a lift, check that out, that is true. Anyway, we've got 3 tickets for The, uh, Fall, sorry, 3 pairs of tickets for The Fall who are performing tonight, at the Kentish Town Forum, if you'd like to win them, here's a question for you - which Radio 1, rival station, which Radio 1 personality used to be a member of The Fall. If you know then you can get in touch on 087008001234."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":187,"End":205,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Anyway, next time you're in a lift, check that out, that is true. Anyway, we've got 3 tickets for The, uh, Fall, sorry, 3 pairs of tickets for The Fall who are performing tonight, at the Kentish Town Forum, if you'd like to win them, here's a question for you - which Radio 1, rival station, which Radio 1 personality used to be a member of The Fall. If you know then you can get in touch on 087008001234."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Uh, or it’s [email protected]"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":6,"End":18,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Is it Chris Moyles? Is it Chris Moyles?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":6,"End":18,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Is it Chris Moyles? Is it Chris Moyles?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":6,"End":15,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Is it John Peel?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Emma B."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Radiohead - Paranoid Android"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Xfm would like to apologise for material broadcast on November the 8th on the breakfast show with Christian O'Connell. The show featured the comedian and author Ben Elton. Xfm would like to point out that during live interviews we cannot realistically expect to control the language and content of our guest's material. However Christian would like to offer a full and frank apology for the fact that Mr. Elton appeared to have overdosed on the arsehole tablets that morning. Christian would like you to know that the dullard will never be on again. We really are sorry."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":98,"End":117,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Xfm would like to apologise for material broadcast on November the 8th on the breakfast show with Christian O'Connell. The show featured the comedian and author Ben Elton. Xfm would like to point out that during live interviews we cannot realistically expect to control the language and content of our guest's material. However Christian would like to offer a full and frank apology for the fact that Mr. Elton appeared to have overdosed on the arsehole tablets that morning. Christian would like you to know that the dullard will never be on again. We really are sorry."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":161,"End":170,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Xfm would like to apologise for material broadcast on November the 8th on the breakfast show with Christian O'Connell. The show featured the comedian and author Ben Elton. Xfm would like to point out that during live interviews we cannot realistically expect to control the language and content of our guest's material. However Christian would like to offer a full and frank apology for the fact that Mr. Elton appeared to have overdosed on the arsehole tablets that morning. Christian would like you to know that the dullard will never be on again. We really are sorry."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Xfm would like to apologise for material broadcast on November the 8th on the breakfast show with Christian O'Connell. The show featured the comedian and author Ben Elton. Xfm would like to point out that during live interviews we cannot realistically expect to control the language and content of our guest's material. However Christian would like to offer a full and frank apology for the fact that Mr. Elton appeared to have overdosed on the arsehole tablets that morning. Christian would like you to know that the dullard will never be on again. We really are sorry."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":98,"End":107,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Xfm would like to apologise for material broadcast on November the 8th on the breakfast show with Christian O'Connell. The show featured the comedian and author Ben Elton. Xfm would like to point out that during live interviews we cannot realistically expect to control the language and content of our guest's material. However Christian would like to offer a full and frank apology for the fact that Mr. Elton appeared to have overdosed on the arsehole tablets that morning. Christian would like you to know that the dullard will never be on again. We really are sorry."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":401,"End":410,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Xfm would like to apologise for material broadcast on November the 8th on the breakfast show with Christian O'Connell. The show featured the comedian and author Ben Elton. Xfm would like to point out that during live interviews we cannot realistically expect to control the language and content of our guest's material. However Christian would like to offer a full and frank apology for the fact that Mr. Elton appeared to have overdosed on the arsehole tablets that morning. Christian would like you to know that the dullard will never be on again. We really are sorry."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":98,"End":107,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Xfm would like to apologise for material broadcast on November the 8th on the breakfast show with Christian O'Connell. The show featured the comedian and author Ben Elton. Xfm would like to point out that during live interviews we cannot realistically expect to control the language and content of our guest's material. However Christian would like to offer a full and frank apology for the fact that Mr. Elton appeared to have overdosed on the arsehole tablets that morning. Christian would like you to know that the dullard will never be on again. We really are sorry."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":48,"End":57,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"It is indeed. We're just looking at the um, the Polaroids, the tests that photographers do."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Yeah - look at me Rick, there. That's always with me."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":18,"End":22,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Yeah - look at me Rick, there. That's always with me."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ohhh. There was a bloke downstairs thought I was Johnny Vegas! He was goin’ I love those adverts with the monkey! I didn't have the nerve to say \"I'm not him\". At one point he actually said, “ I like that one where he hits you, and I went “Yeah”, he went \"You doing anymore adverts?\", and I went, \"Yeah, I'm doing a couple more\"."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":49,"End":61,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Ohhh. There was a bloke downstairs thought I was Johnny Vegas! He was goin’ I love those adverts with the monkey! I didn't have the nerve to say \"I'm not him\". At one point he actually said, “ I like that one where he hits you, and I went “Yeah”, he went \"You doing anymore adverts?\", and I went, \"Yeah, I'm doing a couple more\"."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Sorry, I'm not really listening Rick, ‘cause I want to say to you, can you get me more square on."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":32,"End":36,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Sorry, I'm not really listening Rick, ‘cause I want to say to you, can you get me more square on."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Alright, calm down Rick! Jeez!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":19,"End":23,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Alright, calm down Rick! Jeez!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Karl what do you make of that - pretty face?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":36,"End":44,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"We were talking um, before about uh Shindler's lifts."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":90,"End":105,"Label":"ORGANIZATION"}],"Text":"And they're famous for that, now do you think the monopoly commissions should investigate Armitage Shanks?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":8,"End":12,"Label":"ORGANIZATION"}],"Text":"Because I've never seen another -"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Yeah. Would you just stop just for a second while we're just, just doin’ –"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ricky laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":14,"End":18,"Label":"ORGANIZATION"}],"Text":"Well exactly, I've got to keep strikin’ poses!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":87,"End":101,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I tell ya’ – I’ve just changed my mind, I wanna, you know the, you remember that George Michael video where he doesn't appear, he just gets supermodels to play him,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And, so, you were talking about Shanks."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":32,"End":38,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And, so, you were talking about Shanks."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":6,"End":12,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Yeah. Shanks. Armitage."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":21,"End":27,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"I don't know who the Shanks people are, I don't think they make anything else though, I've never seen them making anything else other than lavatories, and sinks. They seem to have got that --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":86,"End":90,"Label":"ORGANIZATION"}],"Text":"I don't know who the Shanks people are, I don't think they make anything else though, I've never seen them making anything else other than lavatories, and sinks. They seem to have got that --"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":53,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"But presumably there's someone called Armitage Shanks –"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":3,"End":18,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"On Armatige Shanks."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":3,"End":18,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"On Armitage Shanks. Is “waz a word we can – we can say \"waz\", can't we?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"U2 - Walk On"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":5,"End":9,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"U2 - Walk On"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"U2, Walk On; see I like U2 again now, I liked them in the very early days, then I hated them for about 15 years, and then the last album, this, and beautiful day, I think \"really good\" - they've lost all their pomposity - don't you think?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":8,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"U2, Walk On; see I like U2 again now, I liked them in the very early days, then I hated them for about 15 years, and then the last album, this, and beautiful day, I think \"really good\" - they've lost all their pomposity - don't you think?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":66,"End":71,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I tell you what, I'm not going to argue with him, whoever it was, Steve."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Could well have been \"The Edge\", not sure, could have been Larry Mullen."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":59,"End":71,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Could well have been \"The Edge\", not sure, could have been Larry Mullen."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Real name, David Evans."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":11,"End":22,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Real name, David Evans."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Really - interesting,err Rick, you may recall that some time ago we gave people the opportunity to win tickets to see The Fall performing live at the Kentish Town Forum this evening."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":29,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Really - interesting,err Rick, you may recall that some time ago we gave people the opportunity to win tickets to see The Fall performing live at the Kentish Town Forum this evening."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":122,"End":126,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Really - interesting,err Rick, you may recall that some time ago we gave people the opportunity to win tickets to see The Fall performing live at the Kentish Town Forum this evening."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":150,"End":168,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Really - interesting,err Rick, you may recall that some time ago we gave people the opportunity to win tickets to see The Fall performing live at the Kentish Town Forum this evening."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":13,"End":22,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Supported by Schindler."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Schindler, I know you're a big fan of them, and we have some winners.."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":76,"End":80,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"The question I set was which Radio 1 personality used to be a member of The Fall, we did have some wrong answers, wrong answers included, Gary Davis."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":138,"End":148,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"The question I set was which Radio 1 personality used to be a member of The Fall, we did have some wrong answers, wrong answers included, Gary Davis."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":27,"End":34,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"And of course Ed \"stewpot\" Stewart."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":23,"End":35,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Oh, what's happened to Noel Edmonds? what's happened to lovely Noelly?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Noel is just utterly doomed isn't he - no one will employ him now it seems."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":114,"End":118,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Well, he might, he might be turning down stuff, and therefore might be sort of be waiting for a big comeback with Noel's house party 2002 for all you know."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":65,"End":69,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Oh no, you're right it is libelous, thanks for pointing that out Rick, in case there were any lawyers thinking \"that's not libelous - no actually, good point\"."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Err so the winners are Mina, who's from Finland apparently, according to these notes here, err Mina has won."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":23,"End":27,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Err so the winners are Mina, who's from Finland apparently, according to these notes here, err Mina has won."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":40,"End":47,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Err so the winners are Mina, who's from Finland apparently, according to these notes here, err Mina has won."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":40,"End":47,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Well, how would she have called in from Finland?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":6,"End":10,"Label":"ORGANIZATION"}],"Text":"Well, I've embarrassed myself sorry about that Rick, thanks for tearing me apart, that was fascinating radio. Err.. Vinny's also won, he's from Surrey."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":47,"End":51,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Well, I've embarrassed myself sorry about that Rick, thanks for tearing me apart, that was fascinating radio. Err.. Vinny's also won, he's from Surrey."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":116,"End":121,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Well, I've embarrassed myself sorry about that Rick, thanks for tearing me apart, that was fascinating radio. Err.. Vinny's also won, he's from Surrey."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":144,"End":150,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Well, I've embarrassed myself sorry about that Rick, thanks for tearing me apart, that was fascinating radio. Err.. Vinny's also won, he's from Surrey."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ohh - imagine coming from Surrey!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":26,"End":32,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ohh - imagine coming from Surrey!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":14,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"And Tom Prince from Camden, what a great name, Tom Prince, they're all the lucky winners."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":20,"End":26,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"And Tom Prince from Camden, what a great name, Tom Prince, they're all the lucky winners."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":14,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"And Tom Prince from Camden, what a great name, Tom Prince, they're all the lucky winners."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":136,"End":140,"Label":"ORGANIZATION"}],"Text":"I think we've lost it, no it was really good, the first few weeks, yeah, and even the first hour, but this last 20 minutes, I feel that I've bored myself."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":86,"End":100,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"No but its like you know - we're sorta like your mentors, i'll be harsh - you're like Eliza Dolittle, and we've got lots of little stylists in , like they do with makeovers, or that Faking It. they get in like me and Karl, Karl's working on your looks, I'm doing your personality, we're going to get like stylists in, and you know, coaches, and then you have to do a date, and the woman has to, and there's 3 other blokes, and she has to work out what the freak amongst them is, and you've got to go no one voted for you as the freak."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":217,"End":221,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"No but its like you know - we're sorta like your mentors, i'll be harsh - you're like Eliza Dolittle, and we've got lots of little stylists in , like they do with makeovers, or that Faking It. they get in like me and Karl, Karl's working on your looks, I'm doing your personality, we're going to get like stylists in, and you know, coaches, and then you have to do a date, and the woman has to, and there's 3 other blokes, and she has to work out what the freak amongst them is, and you've got to go no one voted for you as the freak."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":217,"End":221,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"No but its like you know - we're sorta like your mentors, i'll be harsh - you're like Eliza Dolittle, and we've got lots of little stylists in , like they do with makeovers, or that Faking It. they get in like me and Karl, Karl's working on your looks, I'm doing your personality, we're going to get like stylists in, and you know, coaches, and then you have to do a date, and the woman has to, and there's 3 other blokes, and she has to work out what the freak amongst them is, and you've got to go no one voted for you as the freak."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":6,"End":10,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Yeah, Rick, I've known you for 3 years, I don't think you're cut out for that job."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":12,"End":16,"Label":"ORGANIZATION"}],"Text":"Yeah, Rick, I've known you for 3 years, I don't think you're cut out for that job."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":30,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Groove Armada – Super Stylin'"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":13,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Groove Armada - Super Stylin, Xfm 104.9, it's nearly the end of the show Steve, I'm going to try harder next week, I mean, it started off well, and then, I didn't get bored, I just couldn't concentrate."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":16,"End":28,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Groove Armada - Super Stylin, Xfm 104.9, it's nearly the end of the show Steve, I'm going to try harder next week, I mean, it started off well, and then, I didn't get bored, I just couldn't concentrate."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":73,"End":78,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Groove Armada - Super Stylin, Xfm 104.9, it's nearly the end of the show Steve, I'm going to try harder next week, I mean, it started off well, and then, I didn't get bored, I just couldn't concentrate."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":113,"End":117,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I know what you mean, I mean, I thought I tried hard early on with the anecdotes, that embarrassed me, and which Karl just used as venom."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Sure, and I had the woman walking around in my clumpy shoes."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":32,"End":36,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Oh they were classic anecdotes, Rick."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":81,"End":84,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"I loved the 1st hour, there should definitely be a show on Saturday evenings, on Xfm, with Kate Thornton."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":91,"End":104,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I loved the 1st hour, there should definitely be a show on Saturday evenings, on Xfm, with Kate Thornton."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":3,"End":20,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Er Richard Blackwood."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Blackwood would be good."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Moyles in, going \"oh the 1st hour, they used to..\" that would be great wouldn't it?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":33,"End":37,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Yeah, err and in this, you know, Cube says it was a good day you know, simple thing that he didn't use his AK, that's the sort of world he lives in, that's what he's trying to get across."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":10,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Great song."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":24,"End":28,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"I have indeed, it's the Song for the Ladies, Rick, we'll leave people with that, have you seen the film Magnolia?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":37,"End":43,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"I have indeed, it's the Song for the Ladies, Rick, we'll leave people with that, have you seen the film Magnolia?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":45,"End":49,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"I have indeed, it's the Song for the Ladies, Rick, we'll leave people with that, have you seen the film Magnolia?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":104,"End":112,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"I have indeed, it's the Song for the Ladies, Rick, we'll leave people with that, have you seen the film Magnolia?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":26,"End":39,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Made by the guy that made Boogie Nights, absolutely fantastic, Tom Cruise is in it, loads of people, and the soundtrack is entirely written by Aimee Mann. now I don't know if she's normally the sort of person they play on Xfm, but she's a singer-songwriter of great skill, I think, and this is a song that features in one of the most breathtaking moments in the film."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":63,"End":73,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Made by the guy that made Boogie Nights, absolutely fantastic, Tom Cruise is in it, loads of people, and the soundtrack is entirely written by Aimee Mann. now I don't know if she's normally the sort of person they play on Xfm, but she's a singer-songwriter of great skill, I think, and this is a song that features in one of the most breathtaking moments in the film."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":143,"End":153,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Made by the guy that made Boogie Nights, absolutely fantastic, Tom Cruise is in it, loads of people, and the soundtrack is entirely written by Aimee Mann. now I don't know if she's normally the sort of person they play on Xfm, but she's a singer-songwriter of great skill, I think, and this is a song that features in one of the most breathtaking moments in the film."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":222,"End":225,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Made by the guy that made Boogie Nights, absolutely fantastic, Tom Cruise is in it, loads of people, and the soundtrack is entirely written by Aimee Mann. now I don't know if she's normally the sort of person they play on Xfm, but she's a singer-songwriter of great skill, I think, and this is a song that features in one of the most breathtaking moments in the film."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":91,"End":95,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"It is a good song, it's called \"Wise Up\", we'll be playing that in a second, but otherwise Rick, that's it isn't it?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":43,"End":48,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"That is it, what will you be doing tonight Steve?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":30,"End":34,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"What will I be doing tonight, Rick, err, probably gonna be... staying in"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Steve laughs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ooh err... watching some telly.. oh oh yeah."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE"}],"Text":"Ok chill out, do what you want. Will you be...sleeping alone again?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":7,"End":14,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Here's Wise Up, Aimee Mann, enjoy."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":16,"End":26,"Label":"PERSON"}],"Text":"Here's Wise Up, Aimee Mann, enjoy."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":11,"End":24,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Dandy Warhols"}],"Text":"Xfm 104.9, Dandy Warhols, Bohemian Like You. It's the Ricky Gervais Show."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":26,"End":34,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bohemian"}],"Text":"Xfm 104.9, Dandy Warhols, Bohemian Like You. It's the Ricky Gervais Show."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":54,"End":72,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Ricky Gervais Show"}],"Text":"Xfm 104.9, Dandy Warhols, Bohemian Like You. It's the Ricky Gervais Show."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":5,"End":19,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve Merchant"}],"Text":"With Steve Merchant."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":19,"End":23,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Yeah! Exactly, and Karl, who's turned our microphones on."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Whay"}],"Text":"Whay!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ca"}],"Text":"Can’t believe it. Doin’ that."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":20,"End":24,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Doin"}],"Text":"Can’t believe it. Doin’ that."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Good"}],"Text":"Good to see you Karl, good to see you Ricky."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":16,"End":20,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Good to see you Karl, good to see you Ricky."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":43,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"Good to see you Karl, good to see you Ricky."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Cheers"}],"Text":"Cheers, cheers. Now, in a fun filled and music filled show, we've got music and fun."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":59,"End":63,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Song"}],"Text":"Yeah. Uh, we've got um... our Hip-Hop Challenge, we've got Song for the Lovers, Song For The Ladies, we've got a film review, so, just, yeah."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":72,"End":78,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Lovers"}],"Text":"Yeah. Uh, we've got um... our Hip-Hop Challenge, we've got Song for the Lovers, Song For The Ladies, we've got a film review, so, just, yeah."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":59,"End":63,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Song"}],"Text":"Yeah. Uh, we've got um... our Hip-Hop Challenge, we've got Song for the Lovers, Song For The Ladies, we've got a film review, so, just, yeah."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":93,"End":99,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ladies"}],"Text":"Yeah. Uh, we've got um... our Hip-Hop Challenge, we've got Song for the Lovers, Song For The Ladies, we've got a film review, so, just, yeah."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":11,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Magnificent"}],"Text":"Magnificent, had any calls about that Rick? Any, maybe Channel 5 or someone onto you?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":42,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Magnificent, had any calls about that Rick? Any, maybe Channel 5 or someone onto you?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":94,"End":99,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"It’s not like other -- it's a bit, a bit out there. Anything caught your eye, uh, this week Steve?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":5,"End":9,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Well Rick, I uh, I know that both you and I are kind of obsessed with these people who believe in, you know, people who can predict the future, or have got contact with the dead or whatever,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":15,"End":25,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Mystic Meg"}],"Text":"And uh, I know Mystic Meg is a bit of a nonsense, but people do take her seriously. On the cover of The Sun today: Mystic Meg Won Me 15 Million Quid."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":115,"End":132,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Mystic Meg Won Me"}],"Text":"And uh, I know Mystic Meg is a bit of a nonsense, but people do take her seriously. On the cover of The Sun today: Mystic Meg Won Me 15 Million Quid."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Wow"}],"Text":"Wow!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":88,"End":92,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Right, and you're thinking, that's not – that’s a pretty amazing claim, I know that Karl believes in Mystic Meg and all that sort of rubbish, you know. You're thinking, wow, here at last is proof that she has got powers, and you're wondering to yourself, well maybe she predicted the numbers specifically, you know that would be a hell of a --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":105,"End":115,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Mystic Meg"}],"Text":"Right, and you're thinking, that's not – that’s a pretty amazing claim, I know that Karl believes in Mystic Meg and all that sort of rubbish, you know. You're thinking, wow, here at last is proof that she has got powers, and you're wondering to yourself, well maybe she predicted the numbers specifically, you know that would be a hell of a --"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":48,"End":51,"Label":"ORGANIZATION","Text":"Sun"}],"Text":"He says, um, \"I always read my horoscope in The Sun and follow the advice\". Ah, basically, what Meg said was: \"Keep a lottery ticket in a yellow mug, to add luck\". So you're thinking, well Ok, he's kept his ticket in a yellow mug, that's still pretty extraordinary,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":96,"End":99,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Meg"}],"Text":"He says, um, \"I always read my horoscope in The Sun and follow the advice\". Ah, basically, what Meg said was: \"Keep a lottery ticket in a yellow mug, to add luck\". So you're thinking, well Ok, he's kept his ticket in a yellow mug, that's still pretty extraordinary,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":39,"End":42,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Tom"}],"Text":"Mm. \"I didn't have a yellow mug,\" says Tom, \"So I put it in the pages of my mapbook\"... sorry, \"I put the ticket in the pages of my map book, which is yellow”."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":42,"End":52,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Mystic Meg"}],"Text":"Yeah, no, see I don't know much about how Mystic Meg works, I'm assuming maybe there's some kind of pseudo-science that she applies."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":44,"End":47,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Meg"}],"Text":"From that he's thought, “Well I'll ignore Meg's advice, I always do what she says .. if she says put it in a yellow mug, I’ll put it in –“"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":20,"End":37,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Mystic Meg Won Me"}],"Text":"I reckon, I reckon: Mystic Meg Won Me 7 and a Half Million."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Sure"}],"Text":"Sure, sure, yeah. So, I don't know, what, Karl, do you think that's pretty spooky? And weird, unnatural stuff?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":42,"End":46,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Sure, sure, yeah. So, I don't know, what, Karl, do you think that's pretty spooky? And weird, unnatural stuff?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Sor-I"}],"Text":"Sor-I’m just a bit livid today. I wasn't really listenin' to what you were saying."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Yer"}],"Text":"Yer, yeah, you are given to us, go on – wh-what --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Eh"}],"Text":"Eh! Xfm 104.9!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Adam F"}],"Text":"Adam F. and MOP - Stand Clear"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":12,"End":15,"Label":"GPE","Text":"MOP"}],"Text":"Adam F. and MOP - Stand Clear"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Stand"}],"Text":"Stand clear, Adam F, MOP. We all know who's dad Adam F. is."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":13,"End":19,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Adam F"}],"Text":"Stand clear, Adam F, MOP. We all know who's dad Adam F. is."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":21,"End":24,"Label":"GPE","Text":"MOP"}],"Text":"Stand clear, Adam F, MOP. We all know who's dad Adam F. is."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":13,"End":19,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Adam F"}],"Text":"Stand clear, Adam F, MOP. We all know who's dad Adam F. is."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":24,"End":31,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Adam F."}],"Text":"No... We all know who's Adam F.'s dad of. We all of know dads. Do we?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Rick, can you keep it, keep filling, ‘cause I've realised I've left my mobile phone on, and the kind of calls I’m gonna be getting on a Saturday afternoon,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":27,"End":31,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Yeah! Just keep talkin’, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Er"}],"Text":"Er, no one'll notice, just... Oh, that was Adam F. and MOP, Stand clear. We all know Adam F.'s got a dad..."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":43,"End":49,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Adam F"}],"Text":"Er, no one'll notice, just... Oh, that was Adam F. and MOP, Stand clear. We all know Adam F.'s got a dad..."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":55,"End":58,"Label":"GPE","Text":"MOP"}],"Text":"Er, no one'll notice, just... Oh, that was Adam F. and MOP, Stand clear. We all know Adam F.'s got a dad..."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":60,"End":65,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Stand"}],"Text":"Er, no one'll notice, just... Oh, that was Adam F. and MOP, Stand clear. We all know Adam F.'s got a dad..."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":43,"End":50,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Adam F."}],"Text":"Er, no one'll notice, just... Oh, that was Adam F. and MOP, Stand clear. We all know Adam F.'s got a dad..."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Whose Dad"}],"Text":"Whose Dad is Adam F.?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":13,"End":19,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Adam F"}],"Text":"Whose Dad is Adam F.?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":14,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Alvin Stardust"}],"Text":"Alvin Stardust!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":5,"End":17,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Shane Fenton"}],"Text":"Yes, Shane Fenton, that's what the F must be for. You back?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ho"}],"Text":"Ho ho ho! The ladies!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Rick, I know you’re a big um,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Um"}],"Text":"Um, now uh, Rick, I know you're a big trivia fan,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":12,"End":16,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Um, now uh, Rick, I know you're a big trivia fan,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":50,"End":54,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"And I thought to myself, well how can I entertain Rick on Saturday."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Oh"}],"Text":"Oh well, I don’t know. Um, here's one, I don't know if you've heard this one before: Ants –"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE","Text":"And"}],"Text":"And – and, they’ve got alcohol in their blood, so they don’t freeze in winter, and, that's why you never see a lazy ant. It's always working."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Um"}],"Text":"Um, Ok, all right then, this is, uh, this is one I’m throwin’ right at you as well Karl. Uh - there's only one bird that has a penis."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":6,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ok"}],"Text":"Um, Ok, all right then, this is, uh, this is one I’m throwin’ right at you as well Karl. Uh - there's only one bird that has a penis."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":87,"End":91,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Um, Ok, all right then, this is, uh, this is one I’m throwin’ right at you as well Karl. Uh - there's only one bird that has a penis."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Which"}],"Text":"Which bird is it?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ok"}],"Text":"Ok, I'd say... Oh. I'll say, I think I've seen one on this, uh, is it an ostrich?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":33,"End":37,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Right, you're going for ostrich. Karl?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Yep"}],"Text":"Yep, I was gonna way that, before he said it."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Chicken"}],"Text":"Chicken?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"...It"}],"Text":"...It's the poofiest of all birds, innit!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":26,"End":31,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Queen"}],"Text":"\"Oh, I'm protected by the Queen, but I need a knob”. I'd give, if I had to give a knob to any bird, um..."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Good"}],"Text":"Good question!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Vulture"}],"Text":"Vulture!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":21,"End":25,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"What about yourself, Karl? If you could give a knob to any bird? And don't make it rude! “Ooh, if I could give a knob to any bird, I’d made it that Jordan!”"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":152,"End":158,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Jordan"}],"Text":"What about yourself, Karl? If you could give a knob to any bird? And don't make it rude! “Ooh, if I could give a knob to any bird, I’d made it that Jordan!”"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":5,"End":14,"Label":"ORGANIZATION","Text":"bird...It"}],"Text":"What bird...It's gotta be a bird of prey or summat like that hasn't it?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":10,"End":15,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Christmas"}],"Text":"Christmas cards would be like --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":10,"End":15,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":30,"End":34,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Yeah, yeah, quick query there Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":7,"End":11,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Right, Karl do you like cocks?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":7,"End":9,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ok"}],"Text":"Right, Ok, no that's fine, that's fine. I was askin’ if you liked --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Yeah"}],"Text":"Yeah. Well I’m uh, I’m a big fan of, um, tits."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":32,"End":36,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"There’s nothing wrong with -- Karl, don't worry. There's nothing wrong with saying tits and cocks."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ash"}],"Text":"Ash - Sometimes"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":3,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ash"}],"Text":"Ash, and Sometimes, lovely song. Gotta apologise to our producer there, ‘cause he was worried about -- there was nothing wrong with it, it's just like saying you, you know, you like watching birds in the garden --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":33,"End":38,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Gotta"}],"Text":"Ash, and Sometimes, lovely song. Gotta apologise to our producer there, ‘cause he was worried about -- there was nothing wrong with it, it's just like saying you, you know, you like watching birds in the garden --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":39,"End":48,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Gas Light"}],"Text":"One of my favourite things is Fanny by Gas Light."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":37,"End":46,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Moby Dick"}],"Text":"That's interesting, I'm a big fan of Moby Dick."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":31,"End":40,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Moby Dick"}],"Text":"Oh, the – oh yeah, the book. Moby Dick. Not the medical condition,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Steve."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ho-ho"}],"Text":"Ho-ho! That’s always a fun bit!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":45,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Beatles"}],"Text":"I've just remembered that my favorite Beatles song is \"Come Together\"."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":37,"End":41,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Yeah. Now, we're gonna stop this now Karl, ‘cause it's childish... You’re right, I've got a philosophy degree."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":85,"End":89,"Label":"ORGANIZATION","Text":"I've"}],"Text":"Yeah. Now, we're gonna stop this now Karl, ‘cause it's childish... You’re right, I've got a philosophy degree."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":10,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Christ"}],"Text":"For Christ sake, and it's about time --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Right"}],"Text":"Right. Is that Immanuel Kant? The philosopher."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":15,"End":28,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Immanuel Kant"}],"Text":"Right. Is that Immanuel Kant? The philosopher."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Kant"}],"Text":"Kant."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Look"}],"Text":"Look at Karl's face!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":8,"End":12,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Look at Karl's face!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Look"}],"Text":"Look at his face!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Join"}],"Text":"Join in Karl! Undo your trousers, just let it all hang out, let your cock hang out."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":8,"End":12,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Join in Karl! Undo your trousers, just let it all hang out, let your cock hang out."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":14,"End":27,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Stan Boardman"}],"Text":"We'll be like Stan Boardman, when he told the Fokker joke."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":46,"End":52,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Fokker"}],"Text":"We'll be like Stan Boardman, when he told the Fokker joke."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Ian Brown"}],"Text":"Ian Brown - Dolphins Were Monkeys"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Ian Brown"}],"Text":"Ian Brown, Dolphins Were Monkeys."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":11,"End":32,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Dolphins Were Monkeys"}],"Text":"Ian Brown, Dolphins Were Monkeys."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":17,"End":24,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Gervais"}],"Text":"Don't look at me Gervais."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Ask Steve"}],"Text":"Ask Steve!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":12,"End":25,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Sandi Toksvig"}],"Text":"I know, no, Sandi Toksvig's got a tiny cock hasn't she?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":17,"End":20,"Label":"ORGANIZATION","Text":"I'd"}],"Text":"That's libelous, I'd just like to say that Sandi Toksvig has never had a knob."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":43,"End":56,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Sandi Toksvig"}],"Text":"That's libelous, I'd just like to say that Sandi Toksvig has never had a knob."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":18,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Opportunity Knocks"}],"Text":"Opportunity Knocks?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":60,"End":70,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Wayne King"}],"Text":"Yeah. It was a pianist, and this is true, and his name was \"Wayne King\". I - do you like Wayne King?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Karl, what's your opinion on Wayne King?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":29,"End":39,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Wayne King"}],"Text":"Karl, what's your opinion on Wayne King?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":55,"End":59,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"You're not a fan of his work. Ok. No, no, that's fine! Karl! We asked you're opinion mate, and you've given it. And that's all we can ask for."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":18,"End":28,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Wayne King"}],"Text":"Aw. No opinion on Wayne King, at all."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":27,"End":37,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Wayne King"}],"Text":"If you, if you're a fan of Wayne King at home, please get in touch, the email address, uh, I had, [email protected] What was the number again, 08700 800 1234. You know, if you like Wayne King or if, you know,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":27,"End":37,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Wayne King"}],"Text":"If you, if you're a fan of Wayne King at home, please get in touch, the email address, uh, I had, [email protected] What was the number again, 08700 800 1234. You know, if you like Wayne King or if, you know,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Karl sighs"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Karl, what are you talking about, we're asking someone's music opinion, it's a music station, what – you, you’re strange!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":10,"End":15,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":8,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ooooohhh"}],"Text":"Ooooohhh!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Sade"}],"Text":"Sade?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"Ricky and Karl laugh"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":10,"End":14,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Ricky and Karl laugh"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":9,"Label":"GPE","Text":"W-w-which"}],"Text":"W-w-which country is it, Iceland, where it's like, it’s like dark all year."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":32,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Iceland"}],"Text":"W-w-which country is it, Iceland, where it's like, it’s like dark all year."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":18,"End":23,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"No. I was telling Steve before, in fact, I’m not gonna bore you with it. Go on, what, what were we saying about Wayne King?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":114,"End":124,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Wayne King"}],"Text":"No. I was telling Steve before, in fact, I’m not gonna bore you with it. Go on, what, what were we saying about Wayne King?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":3,"End":7,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Oh Karl, play a record!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":26,"End":30,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Oh that’s a disgusting, Karl! You're a pervert!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":16,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Liquido – Play"}],"Text":"Liquido – Play Some Rock"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Liquido"}],"Text":"Liquido, Play Some Rock. That's what we're doing, Steve!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":9,"End":13,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Play"}],"Text":"Liquido, Play Some Rock. That's what we're doing, Steve!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":50,"End":55,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Liquido, Play Some Rock. That's what we're doing, Steve!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":13,"End":19,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Weezer"}],"Text":"Before that, Weezer, Island in the Sun."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":21,"End":27,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Island"}],"Text":"Before that, Weezer, Island in the Sun."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":20,"End":24,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"No, no, no. No, no. Karl, did you see that film last night, \"Gaylords Say No\"?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ummm"}],"Text":"Ummm ... yes."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":52,"End":56,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Ohh. You, you’re always gonna lose with that one. Rick, did you see that film last night \"Gaylords Say No\"?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":11,"End":22,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Oscar Wilde"}],"Text":"That's how Oscar Wilde got caught."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":88,"End":97,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Oscar –"}],"Text":"They went \"Well we've got evidence ... So anyway, cheers M’lud. Oh before you go, uh, Oscar – see that film last night \"Gaylords Say No?”"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":124,"End":139,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Gaylords Say No"}],"Text":"They went \"Well we've got evidence ... So anyway, cheers M’lud. Oh before you go, uh, Oscar – see that film last night \"Gaylords Say No?”"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":8,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Children"}],"Text":"Children in Need last night, Rick. Ho-ho!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":12,"End":16,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Need"}],"Text":"Children in Need last night, Rick. Ho-ho!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":29,"End":33,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Children in Need last night, Rick. Ho-ho!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":29,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Did you watch any of it, Karl. It's awful isn't it?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":45,"End":49,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"I've"}],"Text":"It's the worst thing ever, I mean it just -- I've said this before, the thing about Children in Need, it makes the whole country and BBC 1 for one day into just one big school fete."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":84,"End":92,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Children"}],"Text":"It's the worst thing ever, I mean it just -- I've said this before, the thing about Children in Need, it makes the whole country and BBC 1 for one day into just one big school fete."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":96,"End":100,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Need"}],"Text":"It's the worst thing ever, I mean it just -- I've said this before, the thing about Children in Need, it makes the whole country and BBC 1 for one day into just one big school fete."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":7,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"God"}],"Text":"Oh, God!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":59,"End":70,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Terry Wogan"}],"Text":"‘Cause it’s just - they may as well, because there was Terry Wogan at one point going around the audience, with a bucket, just rattlin’ it, getting people, members of the audience to put loose change in a bucket! I’m just - it's national television!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Does"}],"Text":"Does -does he get paid?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":149,"End":151,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ok"}],"Text":"And um, I, I was watching it quite late, we just had it on in the corner while we were chatting and stuff, and um, about 1 o’clock in the morning, Ok, they'd, they’d been promising this for ages. It was a couple of, sort of Hollyoaks stars or something,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":228,"End":237,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Hollyoaks"}],"Text":"And um, I, I was watching it quite late, we just had it on in the corner while we were chatting and stuff, and um, about 1 o’clock in the morning, Ok, they'd, they’d been promising this for ages. It was a couple of, sort of Hollyoaks stars or something,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Male"}],"Text":"Male, male stars were gonna be part of a male stripper – striptease, the Full Monty type thing."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":27,"End":32,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"I didn't wanna watch that, Steve."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":5,"End":9,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Yes, Karl's got you!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":34,"End":38,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Well you've got the measure of me Karl!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":18,"End":23,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"It's a bit weird, Steve!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":34,"End":49,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Gaylords Say No"}],"Text":"Did you see that film last night, Gaylords Say No?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":117,"End":122,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Agnes"}],"Text":"It was like a 40 year old woman, it's like it was 1 in the morning, she'd fallen asleep and her friend must've gone \"Agnes, Agnes -- quick put your glasses on. Wake up, they're getting their cocks out”. And I mean cocks."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":52,"End":60,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Children"}],"Text":"What're you talking about, it was appalling! It’s Children In Need!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":64,"End":68,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Need"}],"Text":"What're you talking about, it was appalling! It’s Children In Need!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":82,"End":85,"Label":"GPE","Text":"BBC"}],"Text":"No but it was just – it was, it was offensive. I was offended by it. It was the BBC, it was charity, and there were blokes with their todgers almost out."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":181,"End":189,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Children"}],"Text":"No! That's not right! It's for children! 'Cause a lot of children will stay up and watch that, their parents will sort of go \"Yeah, it's fine”, y'know, \"You can stay up and watch Children In Need, that's for kids”."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":193,"End":197,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Need"}],"Text":"No! That's not right! It's for children! 'Cause a lot of children will stay up and watch that, their parents will sort of go \"Yeah, it's fine”, y'know, \"You can stay up and watch Children In Need, that's for kids”."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":13,"End":17,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Yeah, me and Karl, Karl's—"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Me"}],"Text":"Me and Karl are looking at each other."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":7,"End":11,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Me and Karl are looking at each other."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":74,"End":76,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ok"}],"Text":"What's happened to us, yeah, just for one week only we're back at school, Ok, there's innuendos, we laugh when we say the word bender, cock, uh, tits meaning birds --"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Karl and Ricky sitting in a tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G. Rick, have you been enjoying Bubba Sparxxx's current hit -- Ugly, you're ugly, oh I'm ugly, ugly. A song which means nothing to me actually, I don’t -"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":9,"End":14,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"Karl and Ricky sitting in a tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G. Rick, have you been enjoying Bubba Sparxxx's current hit -- Ugly, you're ugly, oh I'm ugly, ugly. A song which means nothing to me actually, I don’t -"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":34,"End":47,"Label":"GPE","Text":"K-I-S-S-I-N-G"}],"Text":"Karl and Ricky sitting in a tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G. Rick, have you been enjoying Bubba Sparxxx's current hit -- Ugly, you're ugly, oh I'm ugly, ugly. A song which means nothing to me actually, I don’t -"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":9,"End":13,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Karl and Ricky sitting in a tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G. Rick, have you been enjoying Bubba Sparxxx's current hit -- Ugly, you're ugly, oh I'm ugly, ugly. A song which means nothing to me actually, I don’t -"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":78,"End":91,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Bubba Sparxxx"}],"Text":"Karl and Ricky sitting in a tree, K-I-S-S-I-N-G. Rick, have you been enjoying Bubba Sparxxx's current hit -- Ugly, you're ugly, oh I'm ugly, ugly. A song which means nothing to me actually, I don’t -"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":20,"End":25,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bubba"}],"Text":"What do you make of Bubba?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":7,"End":12,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bubba"}],"Text":"I like Bubba."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":61,"End":66,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bubba"}],"Text":"I know where this is going. I bet you've got a little bit of Bubba in your Hip Hop Challenge."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ho"}],"Text":"Ho ho ho! Well, we did have the Hip Hop Challenge a couple of weeks ago, but I lost, so basically we're just playing a favourite hip hop track of ours aren't we, each week -"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":36,"End":41,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bubba"}],"Text":"And this is my selection, it's from Bubba's current album, it's not the hit \"Ugly\", it's uhj, the album's actually called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\" and I believe this song presumably comes from that title 'cause it's called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\". Enjoy it, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":123,"End":132,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Dark Days"}],"Text":"And this is my selection, it's from Bubba's current album, it's not the hit \"Ugly\", it's uhj, the album's actually called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\" and I believe this song presumably comes from that title 'cause it's called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\". Enjoy it, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":134,"End":147,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bright Nights"}],"Text":"And this is my selection, it's from Bubba's current album, it's not the hit \"Ugly\", it's uhj, the album's actually called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\" and I believe this song presumably comes from that title 'cause it's called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\". Enjoy it, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":123,"End":132,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Dark Days"}],"Text":"And this is my selection, it's from Bubba's current album, it's not the hit \"Ugly\", it's uhj, the album's actually called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\" and I believe this song presumably comes from that title 'cause it's called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\". Enjoy it, Rick."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":263,"End":267,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"And this is my selection, it's from Bubba's current album, it's not the hit \"Ugly\", it's uhj, the album's actually called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\" and I believe this song presumably comes from that title 'cause it's called \"Dark Days, Bright Nights\". Enjoy it, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":27,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Bubba Sparxxx – Dark Days"}],"Text":"Bubba Sparxxx – Dark Days, Bright Nights"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":13,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Bubba Sparxxx"}],"Text":"Bubba Sparxxx, Dark Days, Bright Nights. Title track of his current album. Rick, what do you make of it?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":15,"End":24,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Dark Days"}],"Text":"Bubba Sparxxx, Dark Days, Bright Nights. Title track of his current album. Rick, what do you make of it?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":26,"End":39,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bright Nights"}],"Text":"Bubba Sparxxx, Dark Days, Bright Nights. Title track of his current album. Rick, what do you make of it?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":41,"End":46,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Title"}],"Text":"Bubba Sparxxx, Dark Days, Bright Nights. Title track of his current album. Rick, what do you make of it?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":75,"End":79,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Bubba Sparxxx, Dark Days, Bright Nights. Title track of his current album. Rick, what do you make of it?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":84,"End":97,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Stevie Wonder"}],"Text":"It's great, it's hypnotic, it’s – aw. The chorus, is that a son- it sounds like Stevie Wonder, or -"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":19,"End":24,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"It does sound like Steve, I uh, I don't know, I haven't got the inlay sleeve to hand, I can't tell you."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Does"}],"Text":"Does anyone know? Maybe they could call in."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Rick, uh, I'd love to give out the number, in fact I will: 08700 800 1234, [email protected] Who is, uh, providing the chorus for Bubba Sparxxx’s Dark Days, Bright Nights. 104.9 Xfm."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":131,"End":144,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Bubba Sparxxx"}],"Text":"Rick, uh, I'd love to give out the number, in fact I will: 08700 800 1234, [email protected] Who is, uh, providing the chorus for Bubba Sparxxx’s Dark Days, Bright Nights. 104.9 Xfm."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":149,"End":158,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Dark Days"}],"Text":"Rick, uh, I'd love to give out the number, in fact I will: 08700 800 1234, [email protected] Who is, uh, providing the chorus for Bubba Sparxxx’s Dark Days, Bright Nights. 104.9 Xfm."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":160,"End":173,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bright Nights"}],"Text":"Rick, uh, I'd love to give out the number, in fact I will: 08700 800 1234, [email protected] Who is, uh, providing the chorus for Bubba Sparxxx’s Dark Days, Bright Nights. 104.9 Xfm."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":11,"End":25,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Bubba Sparxxxs"}],"Text":"Well, from Bubba Sparxxxs, to S-Sparky Bubbs – those - Sparky Bubb boys, Suede."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":30,"End":48,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"S-Sparky Bubbs –"}],"Text":"Well, from Bubba Sparxxxs, to S-Sparky Bubbs – those - Sparky Bubb boys, Suede."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":32,"End":43,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Sparky Bubb"}],"Text":"Well, from Bubba Sparxxxs, to S-Sparky Bubbs – those - Sparky Bubb boys, Suede."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":75,"End":80,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Suede"}],"Text":"Well, from Bubba Sparxxxs, to S-Sparky Bubbs – those - Sparky Bubb boys, Suede."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Heyyy"}],"Text":"Heyyy! Slick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":7,"End":12,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Slick"}],"Text":"Heyyy! Slick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":10,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Stroke –"}],"Text":"Stroke – Last Nite"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":7,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Strokes"}],"Text":"Strokes, Last Nite on Xfm 104.9 before that, Suede--"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":14,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Beautiful Ones"}],"Text":"Beautiful Ones. Fella just phoned up and said \"You were talking about water fowl before”. Um,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":16,"End":21,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Fella"}],"Text":"Beautiful Ones. Fella just phoned up and said \"You were talking about water fowl before”. Um,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Cocks"}],"Text":"Cocks."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":10,"End":15,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":28,"End":32,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Cock"}],"Text":"So I could have a – yeah. Cock."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Look"}],"Text":"Look, Karl, look don't worry, this is a nice little, no one's gonna complain about this, this is lovely, childish -"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":6,"End":10,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Look, Karl, look don't worry, this is a nice little, no one's gonna complain about this, this is lovely, childish -"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":8,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Childish"}],"Text":"Childish, lovely little innuendo, there's nothing nasty or vicious. There's no hate."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":106,"End":112,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Say No"}],"Text":"Yes he was! He tried to do this, we - we'd done the gaylord --\"Did you see that film last night, Gaylords Say No?\" Karl, trying to get his own back, went \"Did you watch Gaylords last night?\" Brilliant."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":115,"End":119,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Yes he was! He tried to do this, we - we'd done the gaylord --\"Did you see that film last night, Gaylords Say No?\" Karl, trying to get his own back, went \"Did you watch Gaylords last night?\" Brilliant."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":191,"End":200,"Label":"LOCATION","Text":"Brilliant"}],"Text":"Yes he was! He tried to do this, we - we'd done the gaylord --\"Did you see that film last night, Gaylords Say No?\" Karl, trying to get his own back, went \"Did you watch Gaylords last night?\" Brilliant."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":50,"End":65,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Gaylords Say No"}],"Text":"It's gotta be, \"Did you see that film last night, Gaylords Say No?\", and then you say \"No\", and we all point and laugh."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":15,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Robinson Crusoe"}],"Text":"Robinson Crusoe."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":20,"End":24,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Nice one. High five Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":2,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Um"}],"Text":"Um, we were talking about Children in Need, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":26,"End":34,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Children"}],"Text":"Um, we were talking about Children in Need, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":42,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Need"}],"Text":"Um, we were talking about Children in Need, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":44,"End":48,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"Um, we were talking about Children in Need, Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":10,"End":14,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"And um... Karl what's wrong with you?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":10,"End":15,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Ricky and Steve laugh"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":26,"End":34,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Children"}],"Text":"We were talkin’ ‘bout Children in Need earlier, and uh, as I say, I'm not a fan of it, and I - this was a couple of years ago, I was working um... and we had to drive up to er... to Blackpool."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":38,"End":42,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Need"}],"Text":"We were talkin’ ‘bout Children in Need earlier, and uh, as I say, I'm not a fan of it, and I - this was a couple of years ago, I was working um... and we had to drive up to er... to Blackpool."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":186,"End":195,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Blackpool"}],"Text":"We were talkin’ ‘bout Children in Need earlier, and uh, as I say, I'm not a fan of it, and I - this was a couple of years ago, I was working um... and we had to drive up to er... to Blackpool."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":109,"End":112,"Label":"GPE","Text":"BBC"}],"Text":"And so, it was Comic Relief night, it was a Friday night, and we were listening to all the different kind of BBC radio stations 'cause they all cover Comic Relief, they all sort of link up as one big thing--"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":176,"End":181,"Label":"GPE","Text":"DJing"}],"Text":"And uh, I think this was maybe like sort of, I dunno, BBC Solihull or something, and uh … they've always got like, they've got this, this one guy in the studio doing all the DJing, and um there's some bloke who's sort of outside the BBC with some kids and whatever else, um, kind of doing a live linkup. And the guy outside was Steve Baxter, I forget the name of the DJ inside--"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":330,"End":342,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve Baxter"}],"Text":"And uh, I think this was maybe like sort of, I dunno, BBC Solihull or something, and uh … they've always got like, they've got this, this one guy in the studio doing all the DJing, and um there's some bloke who's sort of outside the BBC with some kids and whatever else, um, kind of doing a live linkup. And the guy outside was Steve Baxter, I forget the name of the DJ inside--"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":161,"End":173,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve Baxter"}],"Text":"He just said, \"I seem to have run out of words”. And we were like listening like ... Ok ... And he just went, \"I seem to have run out of words … I wonder if Steve Baxter's got any for me”."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":16,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve Baxter"}],"Text":"And Steve Baxter's just outside like obviously not, not ready, just going, “Do what – mate?”"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":36,"End":40,"Label":"ORGANIZATION","Text":"I've"}],"Text":"So he just thought that, that's it, I've -"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":92,"End":104,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve Baxter"}],"Text":"It was a hideous blunder, so we were um … we were, we were enjoying that, and the work of Steve Baxter, and er, we were driving along, and then, we were driving along, and we got stuck in this, this jam on the way up to Blackpool, and I saw this kind of white Mercedes, like a couple... and I thought, that looks quite swank, y'know, and I’m – swank,"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":222,"End":231,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Blackpool"}],"Text":"It was a hideous blunder, so we were um … we were, we were enjoying that, and the work of Steve Baxter, and er, we were driving along, and then, we were driving along, and we got stuck in this, this jam on the way up to Blackpool, and I saw this kind of white Mercedes, like a couple... and I thought, that looks quite swank, y'know, and I’m – swank,"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Green"}],"Text":"Green duck."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":12,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Keith Harris"}],"Text":"Keith Harris."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":12,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Keith Harris"}],"Text":"Keith Harris was there. Orville, as I recall, on the back seat."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":24,"End":31,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Orville"}],"Text":"Keith Harris was there. Orville, as I recall, on the back seat."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":32,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Cuddles"}],"Text":"I didn't, I didn’t see Cuddles, the crazy monkey, I suspect, I imagine he would've popped up at some point just kind of annoying the driver's hair, going crazy."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":50,"End":57,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Cuddles"}],"Text":"No – you’ve got - yeah, you've gotta, I think Cuddles has to go in the boot."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":22,"End":29,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Cuddles"}],"Text":"Yeah, and he, knowing Cuddles he'd put his hands over the driver's eyes mucking around."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":41,"End":48,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Orville"}],"Text":"The thing is, what worries me about, um, Orville, is that that argument raged for years between him and Harris, and Orville's right -- he can't fly."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":104,"End":110,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Harris"}],"Text":"The thing is, what worries me about, um, Orville, is that that argument raged for years between him and Harris, and Orville's right -- he can't fly."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":41,"End":48,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Orville"}],"Text":"The thing is, what worries me about, um, Orville, is that that argument raged for years between him and Harris, and Orville's right -- he can't fly."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":21,"End":27,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Harris"}],"Text":"So, I'm worried that Harris will lull him into a false sense of security."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":20,"End":26,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Harris"}],"Text":"Yeah, and then when Harris is out, Orville'll climb onto a chair, onto a windowsill, basically think he can fly and just plummet--"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":35,"End":42,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Orville"}],"Text":"Yeah, and then when Harris is out, Orville'll climb onto a chair, onto a windowsill, basically think he can fly and just plummet--"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":25,"End":32,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Orville"}],"Text":"Just a quick point about Orville - I'm surprised he's still not potty trained."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":5,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Penis"}],"Text":"Penis, sorry. That was a mistake, there I did say cock meaning -"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":27,"End":31,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Rick"}],"Text":"You shouldn't've said that Rick."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bucket"}],"Text":"Bucket and spade."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Bucket"}],"Text":"Bucket."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":4,"End":8,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Oh, Karl, play a record!"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":22,"End":26,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Oh that's outrageous, Karl!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":9,"End":17,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Pumpkins"}],"Text":"Smashing Pumpkins - Untitled"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":9,"End":17,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Pumpkins"}],"Text":"Smashing Pumpkins, Untitled, on Xfm 104.9. I just gotta tell you something Steve, remember, erm, er, at my birthday party, er, my girlfriend had bought me one of those, um, er, arcade games you put money in in a pub."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":19,"End":27,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Untitled"}],"Text":"Smashing Pumpkins, Untitled, on Xfm 104.9. I just gotta tell you something Steve, remember, erm, er, at my birthday party, er, my girlfriend had bought me one of those, um, er, arcade games you put money in in a pub."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":75,"End":80,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Smashing Pumpkins, Untitled, on Xfm 104.9. I just gotta tell you something Steve, remember, erm, er, at my birthday party, er, my girlfriend had bought me one of those, um, er, arcade games you put money in in a pub."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":4,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Quiz"}],"Text":"Quiz machine, yeah, touch the screen right. And we were all playing, but Steve, with his general film knowledge. W -people were getting like 100,000 points and getting through, right. Steve got something like 8 million."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":73,"End":78,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Quiz machine, yeah, touch the screen right. And we were all playing, but Steve, with his general film knowledge. W -people were getting like 100,000 points and getting through, right. Steve got something like 8 million."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":73,"End":78,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Quiz machine, yeah, touch the screen right. And we were all playing, but Steve, with his general film knowledge. W -people were getting like 100,000 points and getting through, right. Steve got something like 8 million."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":12,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Alright Karl"}],"Text":"Alright Karl? Hello!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":189,"End":193,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Rock"}],"Text":"No but it was impossible, and I tried it, and for like months I thought, I just thought I've just gotta knock him off the top. And I did it with all the other catagories, and I was best at Rock, I was best at Rock, let's say that, but by no means as, y'know. The – the gap between right - a friend of mine and a friend of yours, Johnny Candon, the lovely Irish comedian came round last night--"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":189,"End":193,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Rock"}],"Text":"No but it was impossible, and I tried it, and for like months I thought, I just thought I've just gotta knock him off the top. And I did it with all the other catagories, and I was best at Rock, I was best at Rock, let's say that, but by no means as, y'know. The – the gap between right - a friend of mine and a friend of yours, Johnny Candon, the lovely Irish comedian came round last night--"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":331,"End":344,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Johnny Candon"}],"Text":"No but it was impossible, and I tried it, and for like months I thought, I just thought I've just gotta knock him off the top. And I did it with all the other catagories, and I was best at Rock, I was best at Rock, let's say that, but by no means as, y'know. The – the gap between right - a friend of mine and a friend of yours, Johnny Candon, the lovely Irish comedian came round last night--"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":357,"End":362,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Irish"}],"Text":"No but it was impossible, and I tried it, and for like months I thought, I just thought I've just gotta knock him off the top. And I did it with all the other catagories, and I was best at Rock, I was best at Rock, let's say that, but by no means as, y'know. The – the gap between right - a friend of mine and a friend of yours, Johnny Candon, the lovely Irish comedian came round last night--"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":47,"End":53,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Johnny"}],"Text":"Yeah. In fact, he's - you're right, 'cause um, Johnny bought this comic right, he loves Doctor Who, and he bought this comic, and Steve, he left it there, and Steve go a post-it note and on every page wrote \"GEEK\"."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":130,"End":135,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Yeah. In fact, he's - you're right, 'cause um, Johnny bought this comic right, he loves Doctor Who, and he bought this comic, and Steve, he left it there, and Steve go a post-it note and on every page wrote \"GEEK\"."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":130,"End":135,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Yeah. In fact, he's - you're right, 'cause um, Johnny bought this comic right, he loves Doctor Who, and he bought this comic, and Steve, he left it there, and Steve go a post-it note and on every page wrote \"GEEK\"."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":0,"End":6,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Johnny"}],"Text":"Johnny gets it home, reads this, reads it on the tube, and there's \"GEEK\" written everywhere, on every page. That's the sort of vicious man Steve is. He can hand it out, d'you know’t I mean? Imagine him calling you a geek, what could that- what must that feel like, to be called a geek by Steve Merchant? What do you think Karl?"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":140,"End":145,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"Johnny gets it home, reads this, reads it on the tube, and there's \"GEEK\" written everywhere, on every page. That's the sort of vicious man Steve is. He can hand it out, d'you know’t I mean? Imagine him calling you a geek, what could that- what must that feel like, to be called a geek by Steve Merchant? What do you think Karl?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":291,"End":305,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve Merchant"}],"Text":"Johnny gets it home, reads this, reads it on the tube, and there's \"GEEK\" written everywhere, on every page. That's the sort of vicious man Steve is. He can hand it out, d'you know’t I mean? Imagine him calling you a geek, what could that- what must that feel like, to be called a geek by Steve Merchant? What do you think Karl?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":325,"End":329,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Karl"}],"Text":"Johnny gets it home, reads this, reads it on the tube, and there's \"GEEK\" written everywhere, on every page. That's the sort of vicious man Steve is. He can hand it out, d'you know’t I mean? Imagine him calling you a geek, what could that- what must that feel like, to be called a geek by Steve Merchant? What do you think Karl?"}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":56,"End":61,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Steve"}],"Text":"A young lad called up before and said \"Oh, have a go at Steve again and his looks”, and it's not like a game, I'm not like, coming in here every week and wanting to make you look - y'know, come across as an ugly bloke. I don't need to do that."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":50,"End":55,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Ricky"}],"Text":"I didn't have a go at you at all I was talking to Ricky! I haven't had a word, I haven't spoken a word to you!"}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":39,"End":43,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Song"}],"Text":"I tell you what, what we need now is a Song for the Lovers."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":52,"End":58,"Label":"GPE","Text":"Lovers"}],"Text":"I tell you what, what we need now is a Song for the Lovers."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":89,"End":100,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"David Bowie"}],"Text":"I want tell you now, this has been one of my favourite songs for about 20 years, it's by David Bowie; now David Bowie's had his phases, and I liked his glam stuff, and I, y'know, Tin Machine, went off, and y'know, he - he's always sort of, there, on and off, right, but this song is off Space Oddity, it's called Letter To Hermione, and I don't know why he stopped writing songs like this, 'cause this is probably one of the most beautiful songs, ever recorded, and I know Steve agrees with me on this."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":89,"End":100,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"David Bowie"}],"Text":"I want tell you now, this has been one of my favourite songs for about 20 years, it's by David Bowie; now David Bowie's had his phases, and I liked his glam stuff, and I, y'know, Tin Machine, went off, and y'know, he - he's always sort of, there, on and off, right, but this song is off Space Oddity, it's called Letter To Hermione, and I don't know why he stopped writing songs like this, 'cause this is probably one of the most beautiful songs, ever recorded, and I know Steve agrees with me on this."}
{"Accept":true,"Spans":[{"Start":179,"End":190,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Tin Machine"}],"Text":"I want tell you now, this has been one of my favourite songs for about 20 years, it's by David Bowie; now David Bowie's had his phases, and I liked his glam stuff, and I, y'know, Tin Machine, went off, and y'know, he - he's always sort of, there, on and off, right, but this song is off Space Oddity, it's called Letter To Hermione, and I don't know why he stopped writing songs like this, 'cause this is probably one of the most beautiful songs, ever recorded, and I know Steve agrees with me on this."}
{"Accept":false,"Spans":[{"Start":287,"End":299,"Label":"PERSON","Text":"Space Oddity"}],"Text":"I want tell you now, this has been one of my favourite songs for about 20 years, it's by David Bowie; now David Bowie's had his phases, and I liked his glam stuff, and I, y'know, Tin Machine, went off, and y'know, he - he's always sort of, there, on and off, right, but this song is off Space Oddity, it's called Letter To Hermione, and I don't know why he stopped writing songs like this, 'cause this is probably one of the most beautiful songs, ever recorded, and I know Steve agrees with me on this."}
